https://hopectarr.com/privacy-policy/

sign up for Hope’s newsletter to receive news and updates
Connect with me:
Privacy Policy
BY VISITING hopectarr.com, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.
Thank you for using our Website. This statement discloses the privacy policy for hopectarr.com (the “Website”). Questions for clarification of this statement or comments may be addressed via email to: authorhopetarr@gmail.com.
We adopted this Privacy Policy to further the relationship between our customers and us. This statement of our Privacy Policy makes disclosures concerning our collection of information, including personal information, when you use the Website, and how we use and disclose it to others. By using the Website you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect
We collect personal and non-personal information when you provide it to us in the course of using our Website. The personal information that we may collect includes your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information. The non-personal information that we may collect includes your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address. The non-personal information is not used by us to personally identify you and is not readily usable for that purpose.
When you subscribe to our service or otherwise make a purchase through our Website we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, email address, and other information that we request during the registration process.
In addition, if you communicate with us regarding the Website or any of our services or products we collect any information that you provide to us during the course of our communication.
We may use analytic and reporting technologies to record non-personal information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, click patterns, and the dates and times that the Website and our services are accessed by you. We may contract with a third party to help us manage, monitor and optimize our Website and measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and use of the Website. We may use cookies (described below) for this purpose.
Our Use of Information for Internal Purposes
We use your personal information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Website and the products and services we offer and sell, to collect credit card payments for subscription fees and other purchases you make, and to provide customer support.
We use the non-personal information we collect to track the use of the Website and to assist us in providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Website and the services and products we offer and sell.
Our Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties
We will disclose your personal information to protect or enforce our legal rights and policies, to protect or enforce the legal rights of a third party, or as we in good faith believe we are required to do so by law (such as to comply with a subpoena or court order, for example).
We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Website and the services we provide and the services and products we offer and sell and such third parties may have access to your personal information in order to perform their services. For example, we use a third party to process payments made to us, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations. We may contract with third party contractors to help us manage, monitor and optimize our Website and the services and products we offer and sell. We may also use third party contractors to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, and communications. We will enter into confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements with all third parties that have access to your personal information which will prohibit them from using or disclosing your personal information except for the purpose of providing services to use. We intend to take commercially reasonable steps to enforce such non-disclosure and confidentiality agreements if and when we become aware of any violations.
Our Disclosure of Non-Personal Information to Third Parties
We may disclose non-personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information.
Our Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We will use cookies to track your use of the Website and the services and products we offer and sell, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to facilitate your logging in to the Website. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly or at all.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
We consider protecting the security of your personal information as extremely important. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (sometimes referred to as “SSL”).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee absolute security. We are not responsible for the unauthorized acts of others and we assume no liability for any disclosure of information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access (such as through hacking) or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.
Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information
You may obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your personal information by emailing us at authorhopetarr@gmail.com. If you do desire to obtain a copy of your personal information, you will be required to provide proof of your identity. If your personal information changes or if you no longer want to subscribe to or use the Website, you may correct, update or deactivate your personal information and your account through the account management screen. If you wish to deactivate or terminate your subscription you may also contact our customer service.
Application of Privacy Policy You Access Third Party Websites
You will be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use personal information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your personal information to its provider.
Children’s Privacy
To access or use our Website, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from using the Site. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children that we know to be under the age of 18. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 18.
Opting-Out From Receiving Communications
You may opt-out from having your personal information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product or service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you may indicate your preference on our order form.
If you no longer wish to receive any promotional or other communications from us, you may opt-out by following the instructions included in each email communication or by emailing us at authorhopetarr@gmail.com.
Changes in Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Privacy Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. We will notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy by posting those changes on this page.
Updated: January 2017
AFFILIATE DISCLAIMER
I may be an affiliate for products that I recommend. If you purchase those items through my links I will earn a commission. You will not pay more when buying a product through my link. In fact, I oftentimes am able to negotiate a lower rate (or bonuses) not available elsewhere.
Plus, when you order through my link, it helps me to continue to offer you lots of free stuff. Thank you, in advance for your support!
Hope is the author of four screenplays and twenty-five historical and contemporary romances. Browse past works
If the Shoe Fits…
MORE INFO
Happy Birthday, 19th Amendment!
MORE INFO
The Haunting is OUT in Ebook and Audiobook
MORE INFO
Use these hashtags to follow Hope on social media:
#IRISHEYES – Fun (and occasionally bizarre) factoids about Ireland, and the Irish experience in New York, with a focus on the NYC neighborhoods and sites featured in the book.
#HISTORYMATTERS – More of the aforementioned fun factoids only about history in general.
Search for:
Recent Posts
If the Shoe Fits…
Happy Birthday, 19th Amendment!
The Haunting is OUT in Ebook and Audiobook
Hurry! Get ALL FOUR Suddenly Cinderella Ebooks for 99 Cents/ea thru 4/6
Copyright © 2020 Hope C. Tarr. All rights reserved.
